THIPPHAPONE KEOVILAY

Miami, FL | (507) 329-2409 | Thip.Keovilay@gmail.com

Linked In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/thipkeovilay/ | GitHub: https://github.com/thipkeovilay/ | Portfolio: https://thipkeovilay.netlify.app/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Military Veteran with 8 years of proven experience in building exceptional relationships with keen skills, high level of initiative, attention to detail, and commitment to excellence and growth. Proven performance in linking corporate vision with the delivery of desired results through empowerment, development, and utilization of people, processes, and technology.

AREA OF EXPERTISE

TECH

JavaScript, React.js, HTML, CSS, API, Git, GitHub, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Node.js, Firebase, VS Code.

Tech driven development – Jest, Trello, Microsoft Office Suite 365, Adobe Pro, SharePoint, MacOS/Windows/Linux

INTERPERSONAL

Leadership, Project Management, Administrative Support, Quality Assurance, Time Management, Written/Verbal Communication, Collaboration, Process Improvement, Strategic Planning, Organizational, quick learner

PROJECTS

Estate Rev: A Real Estate website mixed with a community hub that allows users to search for homes to rent & buy, overview the community, leave and view reviews, as well as manage the home by searching for available services such as plumbing, landscaping and cleaning. [React.js, JavaScript, CSS, Express, Node.js]

<u>Willy Wonka's Shape Factory</u>: A unique web-based game for toddlers to teach and reinforce their shape and colors, through the use of technology. [React.js, JavaScript, CSS, Express, Node.js]

<u>Fall Fansite</u>: A website to showcase what fall is all about, as well as fun things to do and unique facts about the season Fall. [HTML, CSS]

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer | Wyncode Academy

Oct 2020 – Jan 2021

- Led, managed, and collaborated closely with a small team throughout the execution of designing, creating and maintaining web-based project applications
- Client-side: Acquired a robust knowledge base working with JavaScript, CSS, HTML, web frameworks and libraries such as React.js, Bootstrap, React Bootstrap, experience using APIs, and data modeling
- Server-side & database: Composed back-end environment from multiple APIs using Axios, Express and ERD diagrams; utilized MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, & Node.js)

Administrative Supervisor | United States Navy

Jan 2016 - Jun 2020

Managed and led a team of 21 personnel in a fast-paced and high-volume environment with a diverse array
of talents and responsibilities through the quality, control, tracking and processing of all correspondence for
over 6.4K military personnel and civilians

- Performed clerical and administrative duties, including preparing, typing and routing correspondence and reports; organizing and maintaining records and official publications; receiving office visits and handling telephone communications; operating personal computers; performing administrative functions for legal proceedings; and prepare a weekly/monthly report for senior management
- Prepared and executed daily evaluations, fitness reports, awards and correspondence using Microsoft word, access, excel spreadsheet, PowerPoint, Evaluations (NAVFIT98A), Adobe Pro, and online share points
- Revised the department's policies and regulations on a yearly basis in preparation for our annual inspection, resulting in process improvement by 100 percent and increased overall workflow quality and efficiency

President & Treasurer | Moral, Welfare and Recreation

Apr 2016 – Jun 2020

- Coordinated and governed continuous monthly events to establish a positive environment amongst employees; led a team of 10 in the planning and preparation of proposed events for the department
- Worked with a strict budget of \$2.50/quarter/military personnel in managing the department's function operations that include civilian personnel, totaling an average of \$150 per quarter

Customer Service Representative | Human Resources Department

Dec 2017 - Jun 2020

- Implemented customer service training, quality assurance, and resolved numerous customer related issues within the department, vastly taking care of customer service and holding a 98 percent satisfaction rate
- Ensured goals are met in areas including customer satisfaction, safety, quality, and team member performance; enforced and managed changes and interventions to ensure project goals are achieved
- Typed memos, correspondence, reports and other documentation including follow-up letters to customers to ensure their questions were addressed and to assure them of support throughout the life of their membership

Certified Nursing Assistant | Ecumen Meadows

Jan 2015 – Aug 2015

- Provided daily nursing care and assistance to the elderly and disabled in handling the demands of their everyday life; worked closely with residents in the Memory Care Unit that required specialized assistance; developed positive and relational bonds with residents by engaging them in conversation and activities
- Maintained care to include administered medication, personal hygiene support, served meals and recorded vitals; observed residents' conditions and report changes to healthcare professional supervisors
- Provided nurses and family members direct feedback of residents' daily health; responded to any necessary concerns; responded to emergencies by employing training in charting out emergency management plans

Office Assistant/Cashier | Fareway

Feb 2013 - Aug 2015

- Balanced cash registers at the end of the night and generated reports for credit and debit sales
- Scheduling Coordinator for approximately 30 employees; ensured product orders were placed on a weekly basis to account for any items necessary
- Operated scanners, scales, cash registers, and other electronics; accepted payments, ensuring all prices and quantities are accurate and provide a receipt to every customer

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Master of Science (M.B.A) Business Administration, Finance concentration | University of Redlands | 2020 Bachelor of Science (B.S) Business | University of Redlands | 2018 Associate of Arts (A.A) Liberal Arts and Sciences | Minnesota West Community Technical College | 2015 Full Stack Web Developer | Wyncode Academy | 2021

Specialized Military Training:

United Services Military Apprenticeship Program, Office Manager/Administrative Services United Services Military Apprenticeship Program, Computer Operator Legalman Non-Resident Training Course, 14351B Legal Clerk School